Hello, everyone. I am the producer of the role of Gao Qishan.
Now, I will briefly share the purpose of my role in our project.
In the previous video, I shared the purpose of my role.
My project is relatively simple.
In the current project, the quality is not as good as the 3D one.
But we want to improve the quality in this direction.
Our current project is more like a traditional martial arts project.
It uses LOD.
The problem is that many materials are counter-gravity.
In order to make it look good, it is not calculated by the weight.
In order to achieve this effect, I used many techniques.
First, we look at the original painting.
Then we analyze it.
We analyze which materials are used.
We use M.D. to find the materials and on the paint.
Then I use a brush to draw.
On the right is the final M.D. effect.
Then we look at the missing materials.
Right.
Left.
I know that some of you may have encountered many problems.
The first one is that in the clothing department, the most common is this kind of anti-Chinese style.
The second one is that the upper half of the clothes has more layers, at least three layers.
The third one is that the lower half of the clothes has more layers, at least three layers.
If you write it in a natural way, you won't be able to achieve the effect of this kind of anti-Chinese style.
The first one is the collar of the anti-Chinese style.
Look at the collar of the anti-Chinese style.
In order to make it a little more formal,
I will draw a shadow.
It's more three-dimensional.
At this time, if we untie it,
it will be affected by gravity.
This part will fall to the top of the clothes.
So I will draw this effect.
First, fix the nail to the foot of the collar.
Fix the nail to the foot of the collar.
Fix it where you want it to be stiff.
Fix it.
Then adjust your plate.
After adjusting it,
you can use this.
You can use this.
I will add a little bit of shape.
Then I will fix it.
Then it will be more natural.
If you don't use it.
It will be a little bit loose when I fix it.
It will be loose here.
But it doesn't look very natural.
So we have to use the shape.
Then I will fix it.
After that,
I will harden it again.
Fix it again.
And when you're satisfied,
I will fix it.
And fix other parts.
Like this.
The second problem is the wear and tear of the clothes.
When we make clothes, there is a lot of wear and tear.
If you sew it too tightly, there will be a history conflict.
The clothes will shake a lot.
So when we make the film, there must be a certain distance between the film and the film.
We can't pull it very close like we do manual work.
There will be a conflict in the film.
The third problem is that we set the number of layers.
There is a layer here.
You can set the number of layers.
The outer layer is 1 and the outer layer is 2.
If you set the number of layers and then cut it, there will be no conflict.
After you cut all three layers,
you can re-set the number of layers.
Then it will be normal.
There won't be any conflict.
The next problem is that
when we make the clothes, there is a lot of wear and tear.
When we make the clothes, there is a lot of wear and tear.
We have to add the inner layer.
Then we use the inner layer.
We use the seam allowance to make the layer.
The upper layer is the layer and the bottom layer is the layer.
The bottom layer is the wave.
Look at this.
First of all,
we don't connect the seam allowance to the outer layer.
We use a needle to poke the outer layer.
And then make some open operations.
And then we sew it up.
First, you need to make sure that the inner line is aligned with the center line.
First of all, you need to add the inner line to where you need to make the shape.
Then use the sewing method to sew it up.
If you don't need to do it this way, you can just adjust the pattern.
For example, if you stretch the pattern and sew it up, it won't look like this.
It will look like you're pressing it down.
It's not very beautiful.
Now we're working on the basic pattern.
We need to make it look like this.
But now we still need to add the inner line.
So we're using the inner line method.
Using the sewing method, we're using the inner line.
Now we can make the pattern look like this.
See, now we have this kind of folding pattern.
If you want to fold in several layers, add as many inner lines as you need.
You can add more if you want.
After we're done, we need to put it in the belt.
Then it will have a special effect.
This is how it should be.
After we're done with this effect,
it will have a special effect.
We don't want a soft effect.
It will have a special effect.
After we're done,
we need to put it in the belt.
After we're done with this effect,
We need to do it naturally.
We need to do it in the way that we want.
After that, we can remove the inside-line.
After that, we need to do it for a while.
After a short period of time, the shape will become like this.
Then we will stop the resolution.
Then we will use the shape to fix it.
Then we will do it again.
It will gradually form the effect that we want.
It will look like this.
Then we will do it again.
But our original drawing is like this.
The shape of A is like this.
The shape of MD is like this.
In order to achieve this effect,
we will use MD's blower.
This blower.
This effect.
We will blow it to the position we want.
Here is a display blower.
We will activate it.
It will blow slowly.
At this time, we need to adjust the particle diameter.
Otherwise, it will blow up.
Then we will...
It is too late to adjust the position effect.
We will blow it to a certain angle.
Then we will...
We want it to...
How many positions do you want it to be?
Look.
Blow it.
Blow it to the longest position.
Then we will stop.
Then we will turn off the blower.
Then we will let it fall freely.
Until it comes back freely.
After a while,
in the middle,
you can choose the position you want.
Then you can adjust it yourself.
Then now you can...
This is the effect you want.
Then after we have introduced it,
we need to import it.
We need to import it.
This is the layout and the configuration.
Then we...
After we import the trash,
it's a triangle,
and we need to take it apart to adjust its intensity.
we need to import it.
We need to import it.
It is normally used for this kind of trash,
this kind of waste.
This kind of waste.
And then,
First of all,
we need to put things together.
Because when we import it,
once the md is imported,
we can only take a little,
but this is not the case.
So by the time we import it,
there's still a lot of trash left in the trash.
Some of them stand up.
When the material is removed from the surface, we will choose the
The material will be distributed according to the size of the board
After that, we will increase its thickness.
When I make it, it should look like this.
I didn't make its thickness in MD.
It is easier to control its thickness in JV.
Because some thicknesses are hard and round.
After that, we will increase its thickness and print it.
After printing, we will use MD to print its texture.
We will use MD to print its texture details.
Print it.
After printing, we will get a relatively high-quality mold.
Then we will start to make its surface.
Then this small texture.
This is like a printer.
Like Zhang Gege made this in MD.
He made this with MD.
He made it with this wire.
When I made this, I made it with pencil.
Like the little texture on the alpha colour.
After that, we will increase its strength.
The strength of this type of heart has to be adjusted to your fabric texture and fabric.
If you need size, size and other material's strength,
This will increase the power of the material.
After this step,
all the parts and materials
will be used according to this process.
After this step,
the high-voltage circuit is completed.
The next step will be to continue
the same process as before.
This time, I used MD
for the experience.
There are two main points
that I would like to point out.
The first point is that
the MD
is very natural
when it comes to making the material.
It has a high accuracy
and greatly reduces
the time spent
on hand carving.
Because hand carving
requires a very strong
power.
And
it requires a higher
degree of precision.
The second point is that
when we use MD,
we need to use fire
to achieve the desired effect.
Sometimes,
we need to be very careful
with the board.
We need to be very careful
Sometimes,
we need to
adjust the board
according to our
actual situation.
Sometimes,
the board is not
the normal one.
But we will
achieve the desired effect.
When it comes to
the performance of our game,
the board
will not affect
the game.
So,
we need to use fire
to achieve the desired effect.
The third point is that
we use MD.
In fact,
we've used it
quite a long time ago.
We used it
after we started
working on the game.
But we've been
doing some
more
combat painting
recently.
You can't use
MD in this game.
I have a friend who is a new player in the MZ R25.
He has made a lot of new players.
He is very friendly to our 3D game developers.
That's all for today. Thank you.